neosusa.com 2017-06-06

# W.B. Mason

  * 1\. General
  * 2\. Personally-Identifiable Information
  * 3\. Financial Information
  * 4\. Non-Personally-Identifiable Information
  * 5\. Information Collected Automatically
  * 6\. Information We May Place Automatically On Your Computer's Hard Drive
  * 7\. Children
  * 8\. Links to Other Web Sites
  * 9\. Security
  * 10\. Your Acceptance Of These Terms
  * 11\. Changes to These Terms
  * 12\. Whom to Contact

1\. General  
W.B. Mason respects the privacy of every individual who visits wbmason.com, wbharding.wbmason.corp/whobut2008/, b2b.wbmason.com or its related subdomains (the "Web Site"). This Privacy Policy outlines the information W.B. Mason will collect and how we will use that information. This Policy will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared.

2\. Personally-Identifiable Information

 _What information we may collect_

W.B. Mason may ask you for personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, fax number and email address. For example, we request personally-identifiable information when you register as a member of the Web Site or engage in an online shopping transaction. W.B. Mason will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily.

 _How we may use this information_

When you do provide us with personally-identifiable information, W.B. Mason may:

  * Store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve the Web Site, or our products and services;
  * Use and disclose that information to third parties to the extent necessary to provide you with products or services you have requested;
  * Use that information to contact you for informational, marketing and promotional purposes;
  * Share that information with selected third parties who provide products and services which we believe may interest you;
  * Disclose that information to third parties when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) W.B. Mason's rights or property, other members or users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities;
  * Disclose that information to third parties when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; and
  * Transfer such information to successors of our business assets.

Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise stated at the time personally- identifiable information is gathered, we will not provide personally-identifiable information to third parties.

_How you may update the information we collect_  
In case you would like to remove or change some personally-identifiable information, you may do so by contacting our Customer Service Department via the ‘Contact Us’ link on the Web Site. (Remember, however, that removing some or all of your personally-identifiable information may limit your ability to access some or all of the features and services of the Web Site.)

3\. Financial Information  
W.B. Mason may ask you for certain information (such as your credit card number and expiration date) when you order products through the Web Site. W.B. Mason may use this information for processing your order and may share this information with credit card processing companies and any other third party that may need the information in order for your order to be processed. These organizations have their own privacy and data collection practices. W.B. Mason has no responsibility for these independent policies. In case you would like to remove or change some personal financial information, you may do so by contacting our Customer Service Department via the ‘Contact Us’ link on the Web Site. (Remember, however, that removing some or all of your personally-identifiable information may limit your ability to access some or all of the features and services of the Web Site.)

4\. Non-Personally-Identifiable Information  
W.B. Mason may also collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information may include your gender, interests and preferences. W.B. Mason will not collect any such information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. W.B. Mason may share this information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, W.B. Mason may inform a sponsor that the membership of the Web Site is x percent females and y percent males. This data would be used to customize the Web Site's content and advertising, and to deliver a better experience for our members and users.

5\. Information Collected Automatically  
W.B. Mason may also automatically collect information about your use of the Web Site. For example, we may track the number of visitors to our web site by logging Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We may keep track of what pages are visited on our web site so we can monitor the performance and usage of our web site. Also, we may pay attention to what visitors do and do not use on our web site in order to assess the effectiveness of our web site and modify our content or design appropriately. We may use a third-party service provider to collect, aggregate and report this information to us. W.B. Mason may use this information to analyze and enhance the Web Site, and may aggregate this information and share such aggregated information with sponsors and other third parties.

6\. Information We May Place Automatically On Your Computer's Hard Drive  
When you view the Web Site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Web Site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

7\. Children  
The Web Site is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and W.B. Mason does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals.

8\. Links to Other Web Sites  
The Web Site may allow links to various other web sites. W.B. Mason assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites you are able to access through the Web Site. These links to other sites do not imply affiliation or endorsement of a linked site.

9\. Security  
Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online --- for example, via message boards or chat --- that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While W.B. Mason strives to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. The importance of security for all personally-identifiable information associated with our users and members is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally-identifiable information, W.B. Mason can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your personally-identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Your account on the Web Site is password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. W.B. Mason will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Remember to sign out of your account on the Web Site and close your browser window when you have finished. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café.

10\. Your Acceptance Of These Terms  
By using the Web Site, you signify your assent to the W.B. Mason Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Web Site.

11\. Changes to These Terms  
We will post any changes to this Policy on the Web Site. You should visit this page periodically, because your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

12\. Whom to Contact  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact W.B. Mason by mail at: 59 Centre Street, Brockton, MA 02303; by telephone at: 1-888-WBMASON (926-2766); or by clicking on the SupportSupport tab that appears on this site.
